option.com 2014-05-23

# Privacy | Option

**How Option uses your Personal Information**  

Across our business, around the world, Option will only collect, store or use your personal information for specific purposes, and only with your consent. We use your information to support and enhance our relationship with you, for example to process your purchase, provide service and support, and share product, service and company news and offerings with you, or for other legitimate reasons described by law. We do not sell your personal information. We only share your personal data outside the Option family of companies with your consent, as required by law, or with companies that help Option fulfil its obligations with you, and then, only with partners who share Option’s commitment to protecting your privacy and data. At any time you may contact Option with any questions or concerns you may have with respect to this privacy policy. You may also ask at any time to be informed about the personal data that Option holds about you and request, as appropriate, correction or deletion. 

The only information we automatically collect is that related to the use of our web site. This information is anonymous and is gathered through our servers’ log files. These log files record generic information, such as the number of visits our web site receives, the types of browsers used and the number of files downloaded, but never personal information. This log file information allows us to create better content aimed at our viewer’s preferences. 

**Cookies    
**  
Some of our pages use a feature of your browser called a “cookie.” Cookies, by themselves, are not able to extract any personal information from you. This cookie automatically identifies your computer – but not you – to our servers when you visit our site. Unless you specifically tell us, Option will never know who you are, even though we may assign your computer a cookie. Also, Option’s web sites can only read cookies created by Option’s web sites. 

Cookies allow us to personalize our site for you and to provide you with information that fits your needs and desires. For instance, once you register your product online, a cookie is written to your computer so that you will not need to type information in the future to obtain support. 

**Contact**  

Option knows that your privacy is very important to you. We welcome questions and comments regarding this policy, so feel free to contact us at privacy@option.com. Because technologies on the Internet change so quickly, Option reserves the right to modify its Privacy Policy from time to time. More legal information can be found in Option’s Legal Notices Statement.
